mathbuddyonline.com 2019-03-21

# Mathbuddy

**Effective date:** May 25, 2018

**Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. is committed to protecting the privacy of website visitors and does not share personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent. Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. collects information at several different points on the Math Buddy Online web site and related applications and is the sole owner of all information that is collected.**

This policy has been updated to comply with GDPR. We have made some changes in our apps, websites and services for all users and visitors worldwide.

**1) What information does Math Buddy gather/track and how is it used?**

PERSONAL INFORMATION: Because of the nature of our product, we must collect personal information from users during the registration process, including (at minimum) first & last names, email address and a password.

Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. has partnered with various financial service providers for payment processing. **Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. has no access to any of the financial information including credit cards or bank information entered by the user.**

Your email address may be used to send you periodic newsletters from Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Users can opt out of promotional emails at anytime, but will still receive communications such as receipts, confirmation emails and customer service updates that are considered necessary to provide the service to you. We use the information collected to deliver services, process payments, update our records, communicate with you about products and services and generally maintain your accounts with us. **We do not share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons.**

**SESSION RECORDS:** To maintain our quality of service and to assist in the analysis of product performance, we may also gather data about the usage of various features in Math Buddy. The gathered information is used only to ensure the highest quality experience possible when using Math Buddy.

**TRAFFIC PATTERNS:** We also track aggregate traffic patterns throughout our site. However, we do not correlate this information with personally identifiable data about individual users. We do track domain names, browser types and MIME type. Such information will not be passed to third parties without your prior consent unless where required by applicable law.

**COOKIES:** A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. We use cookies to track user scores from activities and also hold some information about sessions. We do not store passwords or any Personal Information about you in the cookies.

We continuously improve our Web sites and utilize different Web analytic tools to help us do so. We are interested in how visitors use our Web sites, what they like and dislike, and where they have problems. The Web beacons used in connection with our Web analytics services do not share any personally identifiable information about our Web site visitors with third parties. Our tools may gather data such as what browser a person uses, what operating systems are used, and what content, products and services are reviewed when visiting or registering for services at one of our Web sites. This information is used solely to assist Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. in maintaining a more effective and useful Web site for our customers.

Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. also partners with selected marketing companies to help us track the effectiveness of our Web sites, generate visitor traffic, and as part of our affiliate referral programs. When a partner refers a visitor to us from any of these sites, they set a Web beacon and a cookie on our site. An ad ID and a partner ID are stored in the cookie, but no personally identifiable information specific to the actual visitor is stored. Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. does not see the cookie; we only include the Web beacon on our page, which results in a request to the partner's servers from the customer browser. We have no control over their use of the cookie after it is placed on our site. 

**2). With whom does Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. share the information?**

Ensuring your privacy is important to us. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties.

We may occasionally employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments, sending postal mail and email, analyzing data and providing marketing assistance. They have access to personal information needed only to perform their functions and may not use it for any other purpose.

**3). Managing your information**

**Data Collection by Our Apps and Revoking Consent**

In order to provide services related to your Parent or School Account, data on how you use the service is needed and you will need to consent to our data collection when you are signed in to an account.

**Deleting Information or Stopping Collection of Information**

You may ask to review the information we have collected and ask us to delete the information or to stop collecting any more information. To do so, please email us at support@mathbuddyonline.com.

 **Retention of Information**

We will retain your account information for as long as you use our services and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain automatically collected information, such as play data on the apps or cookies information, indefinitely, unless you request that we delete it. 

**4). Your consent**

By using our services, you are consenting to our processing of the information you provided to us and information automatically collected as set forth in this Privacy Policy, except where and when you have explicitly declined our data collection or contacted us by email atsupport@mathbuddyonline.com to stop collecting and processing your information.

If you reside outside the U.S., your information will be transferred to the U.S. to be processed and stored in accordance with Privacy Policy and in compliance with U.S. privacy standards and the GDPR. By using our services, you consent to such transfer to and processing in the U.S.

This privacy policy was last updated on May 25, 2018. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make a material change to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website.

**5). Who do I contact if I have any questions?**

For additional inquiries about the privacy of your information, you can contact Concept Learning Technologies Pvt. Ltd. via email at [support@mathbuddyonline.com](mailto:support@mathbuddyonline.com)
